

✓ tlim24@gmail.com
❖ tommy-lim.github.io/
❖ +1 (360) 241-4508
❖ Seattle, WA

in /in/tommy-lim/
O tommy-lim

SUMMARY

SKILLS

I am deeply curious and driven by the opportunity to create tools that will help others. My Development experience is complimented by a chemical engineering background and 4 years optimizing industrial manufacturing.

FRONT-END: AngularJS, ReactJS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize BACK-END: NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Django LANGUAGES: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS VERSION CONTROL: Git and GitHub

PROJECTS

MARKET TRACKER Feb 2017 to Feb 2017

- Responsive full-stack app allows users to research financial news and view stock market data. Logged in users can "watch" and "buy" stocks, analyze "portfolio" performance, and create custom charts.
- Key Technologies: MongoDB, Express, AngularJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap.

TRAVEL EASY Jan 2017 to Jan 2017

- Responsive full-stack app makes comparing weather for multiple cities a breeze. Logged in users can save cities and compare upcoming and historical weather data.
- Key Technologies: PostgreSQL, Express, EJS-Layouts, NodeJS, Materialize.

PICKY EATER Feb 2017 to Feb 2017

- Full-stack app created for GA Hackathon "Making Life Better". Users can search for recipes from multiple sources by name, ingredient, or dietary needs. Logged in users can save recipes and build grocery lists.
- Key Technologies: MongoDB, Express, AngularJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap.

WOLFRAM|BETA Dec 2016 to Dec 2016

- · Responsive app demonstrates simple data manipulations implemented in Javascript. Users can view algorithm code for reference.
- Key Technologies: Express, AngularJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap

EMPLOYMENT

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Full-Stack Web Development Student

Nov 2016 to Mar 2017

- Full-stack web development program with completion of 600+ hrs in class and creating deliverables across 12 weeks.
- Highly focused in implementation of the MEAN stack with introduction to Python and Diagnac.
- · Agile work environments and Git work flows utilized in daily labs and homework as well as one-week project sprints.

EDT-ENZYMATIC DEINKING TECHNOLOGIES, LLC Lead Field Service Engineer

• Developed Excel and VBA-based data visualization and analytics platform used by all Field Engineers.

- Remote and on-site customer responsibility as Lead Data and Graphics Expert for over 20 accounts in 6 countries.
- Built and presented to stakeholders trial reports for Western Region.
- Sole non-executive to present at 2015 Annual Investors' Meeting demonstrating EDT's analytical approach.

Field Service Engineer

Norcross, GA Aug 2013 to Aug 2015

Aug 2015 to Nov 2016

Seattle, WA

- Created and updated analytics databases for Field Service teams.
- Built modules to train new hires on trial analytics and Excel techniques.
- Worked with customers to build custom VBA add-ins improving their data access.
- Designed and analyzed lab-scale DOE projects in Minitab.

BRISTOL-MYERS SQUIBB: ZYMOGENETICS

Upstream Process Development Intern

Seattle, WA Jun 2012 to Aug 2013

- Competitive internship culminating in a company-wide presentation of research and accomplishments.
- · Optimized growth media and fermentation strategies leading to a fivefold increase in cellular growth and production of recombinant protein.
- Contributed to fermentation reactor's process control logic.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Web Development Immersive 2017

University of Washington

B.S. Bioresource Science and Engineering 2013 Major GPA: 3.86 (4.00 scale)

VOLUNTEERING